Oh
Dumpfrog!
Don't burrow me, you big slimy jerk!
You realize that slap of yours
derailed our train, don't you?
Froggy, turn back!
Get out of the way!
We were about to catch up with Sanji, too!
Now apologize!
Dumpfrog!
I'm gonna beat you!
I don't know what's going on out
there right now, but it can't be good.
Hey, are you guys all right?
I guess so.
Help!
My back!
Oh, no!
Our King Bulls are gone!
They disappeared!
No way! But how?
No, we're the ones who disappeared.
Our train probably got
derailed back there. Ah!
Whoa, that's even worse! What now? Hey!
Yeah?
Are we gonna be okay or what?
If we can't make it to Annie's lobby,
I'm gonna be really pissed off!
Shut your trap and give me
a second, try it to work!
Oh, that's weird.
I think there's something funny
going on with this current.
Seems like we're stuck.
Kokoro? Huh?
Do you know which direction to go?
Yeah, of course I do.
When we built the sea trains, we
equipped them with eternal poses?
set to all the islands
with stations on them.
Then we'll be fine.
I'll watch the sea, you just steer. Huh?
You sure that'll help?
I'm a navigator.
I got this I see yeah that's
good to know oh almost
forgot Hey, Yokozuna!
Stop wrestling and get your froggy
butt off of here! Well... Get her!
Get her!
Get away!
What was that?
You're glad I'm still okay?
How sweet.
I know you were just trying to
save me, but you jumped the gun.
These folks didn't kidnap me.
Does this mean Granny can speak frog?
Yeah.
What are you guys looking at?
That ugly old lady is
talking to a giant frog.
Oh, I get it, Granny was a frog all along.
She never quite passed
as a human now, did she?
You realize you guys are gonna
get hit for that later, don't you?
No kidding.
Hello, Straw Hat, Rocket Man.
And you see them yet?
No, I got nothing.
Damn, that stupid frog, that thing must
have sent them flying a million miles away.
Hey, don't start losing hope on me.
We set out to save our bro Franky and
we won't stop till we make it happen.
That's right!
All we can do now is keep on
heading to Annie's Lobby and have
faith that Rocketman is gonna
meet us whenever we get there!
Go! Sodom! Gomorrah!
Huh?
Hey, hold on!
What's that over there?
It looks like there's another train
car floating just ahead of us.
It could be full of enemies.
All right, guys, let's
prepare for battle! Yeah!
Ahoy!
Is anyone in there?
We're the Franky family.
Come out and show yourself.
Hey, I see someone.
What he's really alive you're
not just yanking my chain?
No I heard that he still survived!
I say that's good stupid ice for brains
really had me worried for a while there!
I thought he was dead for sure.
For the record CP9 might
think that they killed him.
I'd keep quiet about it if I were you.
You act tough, but you got a
heart in there like anyone else.
Anyway, we're in trouble now.
The government's got
exactly what they want.
The only woman with the know-how
to bring back an ancient weapon,
and the man with the only
known blueprints for one.
Don't that beat all.
If the government
actually gets that power,
everything's gonna get turned upside down.
First, they'll end the pirate era.
We won't be able to fight back anymore.
And after they're done
with us, just you wait.
They'll turn their guns
on the rest of the world.
I'm telling you, those ancient weapons
are gonna lead all of mankind to ruin.
My master didn't lay down his life
protecting those blueprints for nothing.
Not if I have anything to
say about it, at least.
But still, there's no point in
me making it out of here alone.
You gotta find some way to get
back to Straw Hat, alright?
I can't.
If I'm with them, it will
only bring them suffering.
You're not the one that's hurting them.
Those government bastards may tell
you that your existence is a crime,
but no matter how dangerous
you may be, just being alive,
just being who you are, is never wrong.
Remember, when a ship is
built, no matter what type,
it's neither good nor evil, Franky.
You got that?
Her very existence has
been nothing but a sin.
What you do is your choice, but there's
no right or wrong in who you are.
Hmph!
My goodness, just look at you.
You're covered in scars.
Poor kid.
It's been eight years now.
Eight long years since Tom
was taken away from us.
I've watched you challenge the
C train every day since then.
Again and again.
You were trying to get stronger weren't
you so you will never have to lose
the ones you love ever again so you'll
have the power to protect them don't cry
now's the time for you to put
that training to the death big boy
You remember your old pal Franky, right?
He got taken away by the
bad guys, too, like Tom.
The good news is we're on our
way to save him as we speak.
So, are you up for a fight or what?
Hey, Starhack, I think I
found another friend for you.
Sounds good to me.
Nice job, Monster Granny!
Wait, where is it? Frog Granny?
You gotta tell me these things. Oh?
You call me whatever you like.
Kokoro, I found us a good current
for running to the southwest.
Alright then.
Well, we wasted a little time back
there, but we'll get it back in a flash!
You heard her, Frog!
Let's go!
Cape has arrived! Look sharp!
Congratulations on
completing your mission!
Bring out the criminals!
They're in Call 1!
How are you handling it
on a little more cat?
Do you love it?
I come from all of the RPs! Whoa!
Everyone stand back!
Careful!
That guy bites!
You punks want some of this, huh?
Come on, get him!
Must he be so noisy?
I've never seen them up
close. Pretty intimidating.
That guy's Kaido Flam, right?
No way.
Then the woman must be Nico Robin.
Wow, she's gorgeous.
Open the main gate!
Whoa, what the hell is this crazy place?
A waterfall?
What?
I can't see the bottom!
You sure are a noisy one.
It looks like Luchi and the
others are headed this way.
And they've brought me the best
souvenir I could ever possibly wish for.
At last,
after five long years,
the time has finally come for all
eight members of CP9 to be reunited.
This should be a time of celebration.
But instead, I'll ask...
What's the meaning of this?
Your orders were to assassinate
the leaders of the revolution.
But according to this article,
not only did you kill those
three, but 20 others as well.
What happened?
If you have an excuse,
I'd like to hear it!
Yo-yo!
My most sincere apologies and pardons.
Chief, everything is entirely,
unreservedly, completely my fault.
Stop that, Kumadori.
A real man doesn't bow
his head to anybody.
I'll explain everything
that happened to the Chief,
so shut up and get a hold of yourself.
Yo-yo!
I can't apologize enough.
And so, if need be, I'll shoulder
the blame by taking my own life!
Don't be so melodramatic!
It happened like this, Chief.
We followed the plan to the letter.
We infiltrated their forces and were
all ready for the assassination.
But somehow, the enemy managed
to find out about our plans.
Probably because I was talking
about them all over town, cha-ba-ba!
You again?
What's wrong with you?
And what's the point of having a zipper on
your mouth if you don't
even use a damn thing?
This little buttermouth problem of
yours has got to stop, understand?
We're secret agents,
we've got secrets to keep!
I want to do it on purpose, Cha-pa-pa!
Why don't you cha-pa-pa me?
I can't believe about it now, cha-pa-pa!
There's no need to blame Fukurou!
I don't need a cha-pa-pa!
I take full responsibility!
Who wanna go?
Iron body!
I can't even die right!
Oh, just get it over with, you bastard!
You'll be doing everyone a favor!
We talked about it, cha-ba-ba! God, ah!
You said that...
Enough, I understand.
Hot, hot, hot!
I spilled my coffee again, damn it!
Oh, by the way, I heard
Nero didn't work out.
We gotta hurry!
Can't you bulls go any faster?
So Big Bro Franky sacrificed himself
to save you guys, and now he's...
Yeah, that's right.
He was trying to rescue Robin
and help us escape with her.
Our Big Bro is such a kind-hearted guy!
We need to hurry, or we
won't make it in time.
Look, the lights of the Nightless Island!
It's Eni's lobby!
Really?
I can't believe we made it!
Alright!
Now we can rescue bro!
Nightless Island?
Yeah, the sun never stops
shining there, so it's nightless.
They sometimes call the judicial
island a daytime island.
We found him!
The giant yoghurt!
Luffy!
Hey! Surge!
Who the heck is that?
It's going to be totally fine, okay?
It's Strawhats!
Looks like we caught up
with him, no problem.
Well, now that we've found the others,
it's time for our date
with the world government.
Hell yeah, it is!
Okay, this is it!
Now approaching Innie's lobby!
All hands, get ready for a showdown!
Sniper King from Sniper Island?
For real? That's right.
I'm a close friend of Usopp's.
I'm here because he asked me to
aid you on this perilous journey.
He's a superhero.
I knew it.
I could totally tell
because of the Masked Cave.
Amazing.
I've never seen one before.
So wearing a mask and cape
means he has superpowers?
Of course!
Everybody in a mask and
cape is a superhero!
Oh, really?
Isn't that Usopp?
I'm glad you're safe, Usopp.
That's the long-nosed guy that
busted into the freaky house.
That's the guy that got
taken away with Bro.
Yeah.
Totally. No question.
It's nice to meet you.
Likewise.
That's one of the guys we
met at the shift station.
Can I have your autograph? Sure.
That makes me wonder, where
did Usopp go? He's safe.
There's no need to worry about him.
Anyway, he told me the most important thing
right now is saving your friend Robin.
Then he left.
Yep, he's absolutely right.
So, uh, so where exactly
is this Sniper Island? Hm?
I'll tell you.
Oh the wind carries my name.
It's inside of your heart.
From Sniper Island far away.
Seriously, where?
Oh the wind carries my name?
From Sniper Island far away.
Sing it!
Hey, Nami? Huh?
Yeah? What is it?
Just a second.
The rest of you idiots
should hear this too.
Before we go to rescue Robin,
there's something you need to know.
So there you have it.
Those CP9 guys are controlling Robin by
using her childhood fears against her.
I'm not making excuses for
not being able to save her.
I just wanted to make it clear that
even if we march in to get her back,
it doesn't necessarily mean that
she'll be willing to return with us
None of that matters!
I won't stand for this!
Damn Robert!
It's not her fault!
Of course it is, Nami!
Why doesn't she want us to rescue her?
It doesn't make sense!
Because she doesn't want to feel
responsible for all the awful things that'll
happen to our crew once we do I don't care
about all that if we don't rescue her.
She's gonna be killed.
Isn't she?
There's no way she wants to
die So we're gonna save her.
Well, of course.
She doesn't want to die,
but still let it go.
This doesn't change what we have to do
We'll save her either way.
I'm gonna beat up every last one of them.
There's a new move. I want to try
Hey, guys, take a look at this.
I came to this island once before to
do some maintenance on the railway.
I drew this from what I could remember.
It's a rough sketch of the
overall layout of Annie's lobby.
The Gates of Justice are located
at the back of the island.
The only way to get to them
is through the Tower of Law.
What's that big black thing?
It represents the waterfall. Huh?
Yeah, once we're inside, you'll see.
If we don't rescue Franky
and Nico Robin before they
pass through the main gate
and into the Gates of Justice,
then that's it.
It's over.
And why's that?
It doesn't matter where they take her to,
we'll just keep on fighting
them until we get Robin back!
And explain this before
we left Water 7, remember?
Once we pass that gate,
the only two places we can go are Navy
Headquarters are the Deep Sea Prison.
No matter what happens, we have to settle
this before they reach those rear gates.
Yeah, pretty much.
On top of that, even if we all
rush the island at the same time,
the only ones capable of going up against
those CP9 guys are you, Straw Hats.
After seeing what you can do,
I know how strong you are.
That's why I think you should
stay behind once we get there.
Give us five minutes, then charge
through to the main island in Rocketman.
The Franky family and galley
law will go in first and
break open the main gate in
the main island front gate.
So the train can pass through I'm
sure we'll suffer a lot of casualties!
But remember once you're in keep
going no matter what don't look back.
We've only got a little over
60 people the enemy forces
probably have somewhere
between two and three thousand.
Our best chance for victory
is for you straw has to
concentrate on CP 9 and leave
the rest of the Marines to us.
Right I got it.
We're pulling up to the
front of the island.
While we're here, take a look
at the sky behind Innie's lobby.
Behold the Gates of Justice!
Whoa!
That's huge!
It's not a good idea to
open them all the way.
When it comes time to
send a criminal through,
they only unlatch them just
enough to let them pass.
Behind that gate are some big sea canes.
That part of the sea is
a lot like the Calm Belt,
an eerie body of water cutting
right through the Grand Line.
No normal ship would dare to sail there.
They'd be lost forever.
I don't know how they managed to do it,
but somehow the Navy figured out
a way to make it through safely.
In other words,
it's like the pirate girl said,
you can't take back a criminal
once they pass through those gates.
Any chance of a rescue is going to
have to happen before they open.
Go! No!
Hop to it!
There's no time to lose!
We'll head in first and clear a
path for you, just like we planned!
Give him hell, Straw Hats!
Hey, you two over there, aren't
you supposed to be with us?
Wait, where's Luffy? Huh?
He was here just a second ago.
Isn't that Straw Hat?
Why the hell is he going in on his own?
That crazy Straw Hat didn't
understand the plan at all!
There goes our strategy.
He said, right, I got it, didn't he?
He's really not the
wait-five-minutes type.
Damn, should have known.
He's an impatient one, isn't he?
Yeah! Yeah! Go, Mr. Pirate! Yeah!
Get off, get off!
Too late now!
Let's move!
Sodom, Gomorrah!
Jump over that iron fence and
then break open the main gate!
Yeah!
Go! Go!
Lookit!
What the?
Something just flew over
Whoa, what's up with this place?
What a huge hole?
It looks like the island's
floating or something.
There's someone up on the blackboard.
Shoot him down before he gets away!
Oops, guess they spotted me.
He went inside the main gate.
This is the main gate.
I have an urgent message
for the chief officer.
At the main island front gate.
This is the main gate.
It's an emergency.
This is Spandam.
What's going on?
An intruder somehow
managed to pass through the
main gate and is heading
towards the main island.
Sir.
One intruder.
That's what all this fuss is about.
Surely you can manage to take?
But, sir, you don't understand.
This is the main island front gate.
Intruder sighting confirmed.
Don't worry, we'll take
care of things from here.
Hey there, buddy.
That's far enough.
Do you have the slightest
idea where you are?
Don't take this guy lightly.
Unless my eyes deceive me, then
I'm pretty sure that he's...
The Pirate Straw Hat Luffy!
What?
What was that you just said?
The man with the 100 million fairy bounty!
It is him!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Where's Robin? Huh?
Tell me where Robin is right now!
I can't see the light of a single one.
I can't see the feeling that I've seen.
I can't see if I can't run away.
I can't run away from the future.
I can't see it.
I can't see it ever again.
I can't
see it ever again.